HIREN MORE

Full Stack Developer

↓ +91 7016486711

Maroli, India

hirenmore26@gmail.com in linkedin.com/in/hiren-more/

🕥 github.com/Rainconner 📑 https://stackoverflow.com/users/8423615 🛗 02 Aug 1997

Summary

Three Years of full-stack development experience (.NET Core, Angular, Ionic, REST Web API, Azure Cloud Server). Experience in working agile infrastructure. Creating and maintaining applications that utilize extended features, including, Entity Framework Core Web APIs, and generics to integrate object-oriented techniques and data-manipulation capabilities.

Ready to relocate

Professional Experience

Senior Software Engineer,

Jun 2021 - present | Pune, India

Happiest Minds Technologies Limited

- Implemented and maintained functionalities in .Net Core and Angular.
- Managed, optimized, and updated API endpoints in .NET Core as necessary.
- Worked on ServiceNow Incidents and critical JIRA tickets to make system more robust and prone to intermediate issues.
- Analyzed system performance using New Relic, as well as integrated critical alerts in Microsoft Teams.
- Communicated with client regarding implementation and optimization of various functionalities
- Trained and guided 4 juniors regarding system and best coding practices.

Full Stack Developer, Swabhav techlabs solutions pvt ltd

Aug 2019 – Jun 2021 | Andheri, India

- Built a full-stack web app to allow users to search through audio and listen with custom audio player
- Developed and maintained two-way communication with Clients
- Coordinated with Team Members for API development of RESTful Services for the enterprise product
- Developed full-stack applications across various platforms using latest industry-adopted technologies
- Maximized applications' efficiency, data quality, scope, operability, and flexibility

Skills

.Net Core Angular SQL New Relic C# TypeScript

Education

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Engineering, Mahatma

Aug 2015 – May 2019 | Navsari

Gandhi Institute Of Technical Education And Research Center C.G.P.A: **8.45**

Awards

Insta Award 02 Sep 2021

Award given from HappiesetMinds for dedication towards delivering stories in timely manner as well as for quick learning.

Project of the year, MGITER Collage

02 Jun 2019

Received this award for collage project that had unique functionality like attendance, timetable, Book Store, Assignment Manager.

Interests

Travelling
 Video Games
 Novel reading